LAUREN CHEN

Digital Marketing Specialist

Phone: (212) 256-1414

Email: lauren.chen@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/lauren-chen/

Digital Marketing Specialist with 4+ years of experience in online marketing, branding, and business strategy across music, media, and entertainment industries. Skilled in evaluating financial needs and implementing multipronged digital strategies that increase revenue and drive brand growth.

RELEVANT SKILLS

Digital Data Analytics/Marketing

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

AutoCAD

Microsoft Office

Hootsuite

Salesforce

Slack

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Triangle Music Group, New York, NY

Digital Marketing Specialist

September 2019-Present

- Manage digital sales and streaming accounts to improve brand positioning and growth
- Source and develop new strategic partnerships, social engagements, and advertising opportunities that generate new revenue streams
- Collaborate with internal departments to execute national advertising campaigns, plan global digital distribution, and re-deploy a 1M+ consumer sales and marketing database

Momo Software, New York, NY

Digital Marketing Associate

June 2017-August 2019

- Worked with management to develop and apply digital marketing plans with a focus on driving acquisition and conversion
- Devised and implemented robust digital acquisition plans, ensuring precision in financial reporting, budgets, and forecasts
- Increased conversions by 15% from paid sources (PPC, Grant, Display, and VOD)
- Enhanced conversion rates by 12% via A/B testing landing pages for a better performing conversion funnel

Kingston Digital, New York, NY

Marketing Intern

June 2016-May 2017

- Helped research, write, and edit blog posts for Kingston's website
- Determined relevant keywords and entities for pages using Semrush, Ahrefs, and Page Optimizer Pro

EDUCATION

New York University, New York, NY

May 2017 Bachelor of Arts, Communications, Honors: cum laude (GPA: 3.6/4.0)



Dear Job Seeker,

Our **Hybrid resume template** blends formal formatting with colorful accents to showcase both your personality and your professionalism.

The color in the skills section immediately pulls the hiring manager into your resume. When they see the skills they're seeking, they'll read the rest of your qualifications more closely.

The Hybrid resume template works for any job application, but it's especially useful for creatives who work in <u>marketing</u> or <u>UX design</u>.

If you're still struggling to write your resume, here are some free resources to help you put together a resume that shows employers you're the right person for the job:

- Free Resume Builder
- · How to Write a Resume
- Resume Samples by Industry

Once you have a great resume, pair it with a convincing cover letter using our matching 2022 cover letter template. Here are a few resources to help you write a cover letter that gives your application the boost it needs to land you an interview:

- · Cover Letter Builder
- How to Write a Cover Letter
- Cover Letter Examples by Industry

Best regards,

The Resume Genius team